start with this 2x2 matrix a and
consider the apine linear
Transformations ax and ax + 1 Z these
two Transformations are shown here
applied to the plane now start with any
point in the plane and apply both
Transformations then choose one point at
random and apply both Transformations
again repeat this process over and over
selecting one of the outputs at random
and applying both apine linear
Transformations let's repeat this
process 25,000 times to see what happens
each point is colorcoded yellow or blue
depending on the apine linear
transformation that outputs that point
as we iterate this procedure the points
stay within this enclosed region this
fractal shape is known as the Twin
Dragon and it's the limiting shape or
the attractor of this iterated function
system produced by these two apine
linear transformations